findanyfloor.com 2019-03-08

# Welcome to FindAnyFloor.com

## FindAnyFloor.com® Privacy Policy

We at Bayside USA, LLC are dedicated to protecting your privacy and handling any personally identifiable information we obtain from you with care and respect.

When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as the individual´s name, address, e–mail, and phone number. Personally identifiable information is also referred to in this Privacy Policy as "personal information."

As used in this Privacy Policy, Bayside USA, LLC includes all of its subsidiary and affiliated entities. Bayside USA, LLC is referred to in this Privacy Policy as "we," "us," "our," and "ourselves."The term web site(s) or site(s) includes FindAnyFloor.com® as well as any other web sites operated by Bayside USA, LLC.

**1\. How your Privacy is Protected**

A. Notice. We provide you notice of the information we collect, the types of third parties to which information will be disclosed as well as the choices and means for limiting its disclosure.

B. Choice. You have the ability to opt out of having your personal information disclosed to a third party. For sensitive information, affirmative opt in choices are provided rather than simply an opt out.

C. Access. We provide you access to personal information and allow you to correct, amend, or delete that information where it is inaccurate, except where the rights of persons other than the individual would be violated.

D. Security. We take precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

**2\. OPTING–IN OR OUT**

You may opt–in or out of receiving promotional communications from us upon request through logging on to your account and selecting the appropriate opt–in or opt–out choices.

Please note: even if you opt–out of receiving promotional material, when you purchase or request products or services or specifically request information from us or third parties, promotional materials may accompany the delivery of that product, service or information.

**3\. Information You Provide to Us**

Typically the personally identifiable information we receive comes directly from users like you who are interested in obtaining various products and services from us or from third parties. In general, this information includes the user´s login name, real name, postal address, e–mail address, and telephone number.

We may also collect other types of information such as types of flooring you are interested in, room dimensions, room layouts, room photographs, and other information you provide us regarding products and services you may be interested in. We collect personal information when you register on, log on, or visit our web sites, including when you participate in activities on our web sites, such as using our design tools, search tools sweepstakes, contests, games and promotional offers.

**4\. Information Collected Through Technology**

We collect information through technology to make our sites more interesting and useful. For instance, when you come to one of our sites, your IP address is collected. An IP address is often associated with the network through which you enter the Internet, like your ISP or your company. At times, we also use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our sites. We may also use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our web sites.

When you view our web sites we may store a small amount of information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small files stored on your computer, not on our site. We use cookies in our web tools, to deliver content specific to your interests, and to prevent you from reentering all your registration data at each connection. Through your web browser you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser´s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookie settings.  
Our web sites may also use a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, such as pixel tags. We may also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on our web sites, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our web sites.

Many advertisements are managed and placed on our web sites by third parties. Third–party advertisers who place advertisements on our web sites may also use cookies and pixel tags to collect non–personally identifiable information when you click on or move your cursor over one of their banner advertisements. Once you´ve clicked on an advertisement and have left our web sites, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their site. 

Our website utilizes Google as a third party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our website. Google's, use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our website and other websites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**5\. Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

We may use your personally identifiable information in many ways, including helping you explore flooring options, sending you promotional materials, and sharing your information with third parties so that these third parties can send you promotional materials. We may also supplement personally identifiable information that we have collected directly from our users with other information that we obtain from third party partners. We may also share your personal information with companies we have a relationship with that offer flooring products and/or services.

In addition, we may also share your information when you participate in certain activities on our sites that are sponsored by third parties such as making specific requests for flooring information or participating in contests or games sponsored in whole or in part by a third party.

Finally, sometimes we hire companies to help deliver products or services, like a company that helps fulfill prizes for a contest. In those instances, there is a need to share your information with these companies.

We may also take your personally identifiable information and make it non–personally identifiable, either by combining it with information about other individuals, or by removing characteristics (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. There are no restrictions under this Privacy Policy upon our right to aggregate or de–personalize your personal information, and we may use and/or share the resulting non–personally identifiable information with third parties in any way.

**6\. Purchase or Sale of Businesses**

From time to time we may purchase a business or one or more of our businesses may be sold and your personally identifiable information may be transferred as a part of the purchase or sale.

**7\. Additional Disclosures Required By Law**

We will disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosures are required by law, including, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena; will help to enforce our Terms of Use; enforce contest, sweepstakes, promotions, and/or game rules; protect your safety or security; and/or, protect the safety and security of our web sites, us, and/or third parties, including the safety and security of property that belongs to us or third parties.

**8\. Children's Information**

This site is not directed toward children under thirteen years of age. Bayside USA, LLC does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under thirteen years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, you should not register to become a member or provide any personally identifiable information through the site.

**9\. Applicability**

This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifiable information collected on the web sites where this Privacy Policy is posted and does not apply to any other information collected by Bayside USA, LLC through any other means.

This Privacy Policy applies to use and sharing of personally identifiable information collected on and after the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.
